Criminal Justice, School of; Records ua640
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Dean's Historical Day Files, 1963 April-1971 June; 1; 0.50 cubic ft.
  - Day Files, 1967 September-1968 March; 1.7
    - VISITING COMMITTEE FUNCTION, 11/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 297)
    - BRIEF BIOGRAPHICAL SKETCHES OF THE CHARTER VISITING COMMITTEE MEMBERS, SCJ, 1967 October (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 298)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re 11/16 meeting of Visiting Committee, 10/24/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 299)
    - VISITING COMMITTEE, SCJ, Initial Meeting-Tentative Agenda, 11/15/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 300)
    - A PROPOSAL FOR THE PROGRAMS, DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY (Criminal Justice), MASTER OF ARTS (Criminal Justice), 1967 October (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 301)
    - Memo to Deans and Dept. Chairmen from Dwight Smith, re Space Planning, 10/05/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 302)
    - Memo to Mary Farrington, Faculty, and Mike Feit from Jim Munro, 10/16/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 303)
    - Memo to Webb Fiser from R. Myren, re Recruiting for 1968-69, 10/19/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 304)
    - PROGRAMS for the DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY (Criminal Justice, MASTER OF ARTS (Criminal Justice), 1967 November (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 305)
    - Memo to E. Flinton from Dean R.L. Rice, re Your Memo 1 November regarding SCJ, 11/06/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 306)
    - Memo to E.W. Flinton, Dean of Grad. Stds. from F.J. Tickner, Acting Dean, GSPA re Proposed Programs in Criminal Justice, 11/09/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 307)
    - Memo to Dwight Smith from R. Myren, re Long Range Planning Response of SCJ, 11/10/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 308)
    - Memo to Dean O.W. Perlmutter from Paul Wheeler, re Proposed Graduate program in Criminal Justice, 11/10/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 309)
    - Memo to Dean Myren from Fred Cohen, re Suggestions for Development, 11/20/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 310)
    - Memo to Profs. Brown, Cohen, Munro, Newman and Toch from R. Myren, re Academic proposal, 11/20/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 311)
    - Notice to Earl Droessler for transmission to Chancellor Gould for budget hearings, 1967 November 6-1967 November 13 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 312)
    - Memo to Deans and Dept. Chairmen from Webb Fiser, 11/27/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 313)
    - Memo to R. Myren, Faculty, Mary Farrington, Mike Feit from Hans Toch, re continuing research function for the School of Criminal Justice, 11/30/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 314)
    - Minutes from Graduate Academic Council meeting of, 12/07/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 315)
    - Memo to Alice Hastings from R. Myren, re Library Collection needs School of Criminal Justice, 1968-1969 through 1973-1974, 12/14/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 316)
    - School of Criminal Justice, News and Notes, 12/21/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 317)
    - Letter to Richard Myren from Edward F. Carr, 12/29/1967 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 318)
    - Letter to Miss Judith Glock from Joan M. Dittmer, secretary to E. Lumbard, re visiting committee - Lumbard expenses, 01/02/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 319)
    - 1968-69 Budget for Temporary Service Funds (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 320)
    - Memo to R. Myren from Milton C. Olson, 01/02/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 321)
    - Memo to R. Myren from Webb Fiser, re Budget, 01/18/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 322)
    - Letter to Dr. Harry Porter from Edgar W. Flinton, 01/23/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 323)
    - Memo to Faculty, Dr. Webb Fiser, Dean Edgar Flinton from R. Myren, re Curriculum Committee, School of Criminal Justice, 01/25/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 324)
    - Memo to Faculty, Dr. Webb Fiser, Dean Edgar Flinton from R. A. Myren, re School Executive Committee, 01/29/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 325)
    - Memo to R.A. Myren from Webb Fiser, re approval to hire 3 new people under the 1968-69 budget, 01/30/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 326)
    - PROGRAMS for the DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY - Ph.D. (Criminal Justice), MASTER OF ARTS - M.A. (Criminal Justice), 1968 February (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 327)
    - School of Criminal Justice OUTSIDE FUNDING NEEDS, by R. Myren, 02/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 328)
    - Memo to Dr. Webb Fiser from R. Myren, re Summer Salaries, 02/01/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 329)
    - Letter to Dr. Harry Porter from Allan A. Kuusisto, 02/06/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 330)
    - Memo to R. Myren from Judie, 02/15/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 331)
      re Budget Meeting of 2/14/1968.
    - Memo to Faculty, Webb Fiser, Dean Edgar Flinton from R. Myren, re School Executive Committee, 03/04/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 332)
    - MINUTES OF MEETING - PROGRAMMING WEST PODIUM EXTENSION, 03/13/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 333)
    - Memo to R. Myren from Raymond J. Spenard, re West Podium Extension, 03/14/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 334)
    - Memo to Deans and Department Chairman from Milton Olson, 03/15/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 335)
    - Memo to Deans of Schools from Webb Fiser, re 1968-69 Budget, 03/15/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 336)
    - Memo to Dr. Paul Miwa from Dwight C. Smith, re Space Planning, 03/19/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 337)
    - Memo to R.A. Myren from Paul Miwa, re Faculty Planning Committee for West End Podium Extension, 03/19/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 338)
    - Memo to R.A. Myren from Marilyn D. Galeo, re resignation, 03/21/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 339)
    - Memo to Dr. Webb Fiser from R.A. Myren, re Budget 1968-69, 03/21/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 340)
    - Memo to Dr. Milton Olson, VP Management & Planning from R.A. Myren, re pending secretarial vacancy, 03/27/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 341)
  - Day Files, 1968 April-1968 October; 1.8
    - Tentative Budget Allocations for 1968-69, 04/01/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 342)
    - WEST END PODIUM SPACE NEEDS, SCJ, R. Myren, Dean, 04/04/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 343)
    - Assistantships, Fellowships, Traineeships 1968-69, 04/17/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 344)
    - Memo to Director, Readers' Services from Mary Farrington, re 1969-70 Budget Information, 04/17/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 345)
    - Planning Summary, Visiting Committee Mtg, 10/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 346)
    - Memo to Administrative Officers, Department Chairmen, from Edgar Flinton, Dean of Graduate Studies, re Fellowships and Assistantships for 1968-69: Summary, 04/26/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 347)
    - Memo to R. Myren from F.J. Tickner, re Electro-Magnetic Typewriter, 04/29/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 348)
    - Memo to All Deans and Department Chairmen from Milton Olson VP for Management and Planning, 05/02/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 349)
    - Memo to Dean Myren, re workload positions, 05/09/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 350)
    - Memo to R. Stierer from R. Myren, re Request for MT/ST Rental, 05/13/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 351)
    - Memo to Lloyd Hebert from R. Myren, re Temporary Service, 05/14/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 352)
    - Newspaper Clipping from the Los Angeles Times, Sunday, "New School Will Delve into Crime", by William Trombley, 05/19/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 353)
    - News and Notes, SCJ, SUNYA, 1968 May (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 354)
    - Summary of Official Action on New and Revised Graduate Programs at State University of New York at Albany, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 355)
    - Annual Report Summary Statement, SCJ, SUNYA, 1968 July (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 356)
    - Deans Report, SCJ, SUNYA, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 357)
    - Letter to Mr. Elwin W. Stevens from Walter M. Tisdale, re West Podium Extension, SUNYA, 08/13/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 358)
    - Temporary Faculty By-Laws and Operating Policies, SCJ, SUNYA, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 359)
    - Operating Policies, SCJ, Academic Year 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 360)
    - Memo to Deans from Paul Miwa, re Faculty Planning Committee for West End Podium Expansion, 09/12/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 361)
    - Memo to W. Clarkin from M. Farrington, 09/13/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 362)
      re Amount Committed on Books and Periodicals, April 1, 1968 to September 1, 1968.
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re Visiting Committee, 09/17/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 363)
    - Memo to Dean Myren, Members of the Faculty from H. Toch, 10/01/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 364)
    - Listing of Enrolled Students 1968-69, SCJ, SUNYA, 10/01/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 365)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, re Visiting Committee, 10/08/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 366)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re Visiting Committee, 10/10/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 367)
    - Memo to Faculty from V. O'Leary, 10/14/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 368)
    - Memo to R. Galvin, R. Hardt, D. Newman, V. O'Leary, H. Toch from V. O'Leary re SCJ Committee on Research, 10/16/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 369)
    - Memo to Faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting dates, 10/21/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 370)
    - Letter to Visiting Committee Members from R. Myren, re Visiting Committee Meeting, 10/22/1968-10/24/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 371)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, 10/24/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 372)
    - Memo to R. Myren, from M. Feit, re agenda faculty meeting 11/4/1968, 10/28/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 373)
    - Memo to faculty from D. Newman, re Faculty-Student Relations: A View from Under the Toch, 10/31/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 374)
    - Note regarding student participation in Visiting Committee, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 375)
    - Memo to Faculty from R. Myren, 10/31/1968, re faculty meeting agenda, 11/04/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 376)
  - Day Files, 1968 November-1969 August; 1.9
    - Memo to Faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting, 11/05/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 377)
    - Memo to Faculty from R. Myren, re Report of Faculty Action, 11/4/1968, 11/07/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 378)
    - Memo to Faculty from R. Myren, re Amendment of School By-Laws, 11/07/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 379)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re New Jersey revision proposal, 11/07/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 380)
    - Minutes of Faculty Meeting, 11/08/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 381)
    - SUNYA, SCJ Temporary Faculty By-Laws, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 382)
    - Memo to Faculty from R. Myren, re standing committees, 11/08/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 383)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, re New Jersey Criminal Law Revision, 11/11/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 384)
    - Sample copy of letter to Visiting Committee, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 385)
    - Memo to Newman, Hardt, Toch from V. O'Leary, re Ad Hoc Committee on Qualifying Examinations, 11/13/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 386)
    - Memo to Faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 11/18/1968, 11/14/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 387)
    - Memo to R. Myren from M. O'Neill, re student meeting, 11/15/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 388)
    - Memo from R. Myren to R. Arens, re Proposed series of seminars to be conducted by Professor Harold D. Lasswell, 11/15/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 389)
    - Minutes of Faculty Meeting, 11/18/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 390)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, 11/20/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 391)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, 11/22/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 392)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 12/2/1968, 11/27/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 393)
    - Minutes of Faculty Meeting, 12/02/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 394)
    - December 1968 Enrollment Projections, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 395)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda 12/16/1968, 12/12/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 396)
    - Memo to V. O'Leary from M. O'Neill, re Committee appointments, 12/13/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 397)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto. re minutes of faculty meeting, 12/19/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 398)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re Exam Schedule, 12/20/1968 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 399)
    - Tentative Outline, Library Memo, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 400)
    - CRJ 550, Pro Seminar on Issues in CJ Administration, Course Outline, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 401)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re cancellation of 1/6/1969 meeting, 01/03/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 402)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re agenda for 1/13/1969, 01/10/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 403)
    - Memo to faculty, A. Pasciuto, Mary Farrington from R. Myren, re 1969-71 Bulletin, 01/16/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 404)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Russell N. Fairbanks, 01/17/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 405)
    - Memo to Faculty, Mrs. Farrington, A. Pasciuto, from R. Myren, re Faculty Meeting Agenda for 1/27/1969, 01/20/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 406)
    - Newspaper clipping - Unique Albany State U Program - "Ex-Convicts to Be Students" by Dean Richard A. Myren, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 407)
    - Copy of newspaper article - "Criminal Justice Reforms Urged by SUNY Law Dean", Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 408)
    - News and Notes, SCJ, SUNYA, 02/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 409)
    - News Release from Ford Foundation, 02/05/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 410)
    - Letter to Carl Vergari from R. Myren, 02/06/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 411)
    - Memo to faculty, Mrs. Farrington, Dr. Chappel, A. Pasciuto, student association, from R. Myren, re Faculty Meeting Agenda 2/19/1969, 02/06/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 412)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re special faculty meeting, 02/07/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 413)
    - Enrollment projection worksheet, Fall 1969 and Fall 1970, 02/14/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 414)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, 02/20/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 415)
    - Memo to faculty, Messrs. Chappel, Pasciuto, Mrs. Farrington, from R. Myren, re faculty meeting 2/24/1969, 02/19/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 416)
    - Memo to faculty, Mrs. Farrington, Mr. Chappel, from T. Pasciuto, re minutes of special faculty meeting, 2/24/1969, 03/04/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 417)
    - Letter to Evan R. Collins from Alvin P. Lierheimer, re Corrected Registration, 03/05/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 418)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda 3/10/1969, 03/07/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 419)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, 03/17/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 420)
    - Memo to faculty and students from D. Newman, H. Toch, R. Hardt, re qualifying examination, 03/19/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 421)
    - Copy of Times Union article, "2 State U. Students are Lehman Fellows", 03/18/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 422)
    - Memo to faculty from Dean Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 3/24/1969, 03/20/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 423)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of 3/10/1969 faculty meeting, 03/29/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 424)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of faculty meeting, 03/24/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 425)
    - Memo to faculty from Dean Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 4/7/1969, 04/04/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 426)
    - Memo to faculty from Dean Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 4/21/1969, 04/17/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 427)
    - Memo to faculty, M. Feit, Mrs. Farrington, Prof. Chappell from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of faculty meeting, Monday, 4/7/1969, 04/18/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 428)
    - Student Participation in School Governance, 05/05/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 429)
    - SCJ Operating Policies, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 430)
    - SUNYA, SCJ By-Laws, 05/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 431)
    - SCJ Operating Procedures, 05/05/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 432)
    - Memo to faculty, M. Feit, Prof. Chappell, Mrs. Farrington, H. Sin, Burt Zahler from R. Myren, re annual faculty meeting agenda, 05/09/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 433)
    - Memo to faculty, Mrs. Farrington, Mr. Feit, Dr. Chappell from Tony Pasciuto, re minutes of faculty meeting 5/5/1969, 05/12/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 434)
    - Memo to faculty, Prof. Chappell, Mrs. Farrington, Mr. Pasciuto, Mr. Feit from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 05/15/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 435)
    - SUNYA, SCJ By-Laws, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 436)
    - Memo to faculty, Dean Myren, Prof. Chappell, Mrs. Farrington, M. Feit, re minutes of faculty meeting, Monday, 5/12/1969, 05/19/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 437)
    - Memo to faculty, Mrs. Farrington, Mr. Pasciuto, Dr. Chappell, Mr. Feit from R. Myren, re faculty meetings, 05/29/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 438)
    - SCJ Operating Policies, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 439)
    - SUNYA, SCJ By-Laws, 05/19/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 440)
    - School of Criminal Justice Faculty, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 441)
    - SCJ, SUNYA News and Notes, 1969 June (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 442)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, re Visiting Committee, 08/12/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 443)
    - SCJ, Dean's Report, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 444)
  - Day Files, 1969 September-1970 January; 1.10
    - Operating Policies, School of Criminal Justice, Academic Year 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 445)
    - Suggested Master Schedule Worksheet, Alternative # 1, Expanded Version for Fall 1969, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 446)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 9/9/1969, 09/08/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 447)
    - Requirements and Procedures for the Master's Degree Project, SUNYA, SCJ, 01/13/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 448)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 9/18/1969, 09/16/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 449)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of faculty meeting, 09/18/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 450)
    - SCJ Operating Policies, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 451)
    - SCJ Operating Policies, 09/18/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 452)
    - Memo to R. Myren from Alice Hastings, Univ. Lib., re Clapp-Jordan formula A PROPOSAL TO ESTABLISH AN INTERNATIONAL CONSORTIUM FOR SOCIAL, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 453)
    - POLICY AND CRIMINOLOGICAL RESEARCH WITH SPECIAL REFERENCE TO THE DEVELOPING COUNTRIES OF ASIA, drawn up by: Leslie T. Wilkins, 09/23/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 454)
      (Original 10/1966, Amended 10/1969).
    - Proposed Procedures for admission to Doctoral Candidacy, 10/03/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 455)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 10/6/1969, 10/03/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 456)
    - Letter to Visiting Committee members from R. Myren, 10/06/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 457)
    - Biographical Sketches, student body, SCJ, 10/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 458)
    - Biographical Sketches, Visiting Committee, SCJ, 10/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 459)
    - Visiting Committee, list of participants, meeting, 10/24/1969-10/25/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 460)
    - Visiting Committee, SCJ, SUNYA, 10/24/1969-10/25/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 461)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, re Visiting Committee, 10/28/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 462)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 11/3/1969, 10/29/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 463)
    - Memo to faculty from D. Newman, re The Fourth Area: Issues in CJ, 10/31/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 464)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 11/3/1969, 10/31/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 465)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, 10/31/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 466)
    - SCJ Model Qualifying Examination, Section A, Nature of Crime & Issues in CJ Administration, 11/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 467)
    - SCJ Operating Policy Decision, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 468)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of faculty meeting, 10/6/1969, 11/01/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 469)